Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4051
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Additional Office Files
1950-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor-Management Documentation Center
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
/4051
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7980325
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4049: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4072: Kheel Center Additional Files /4088: Kheel Center Office Files /4090: Kheel Center R. Strassberg Conservation Files /4090: Kheel Center R. Strassberg Conservation Files /4090: Kheel Center R. Strassberg Conservation Files
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Martin P. Catherwood Library; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Labor-Management Documentation Center
7980325
- A, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Amboy Bicentennial Commission, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Archivists, Society of, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Archives & Libraries Balch Institute, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Archives & Libraries Balch Institute, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- C, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Canada, Public Archives of, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Canadian Labor History, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Colorado Railroad Museum, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cornell Medical Center Mss. & Archives, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Libraries - Hays Study, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell University Libraries (memos), 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- D, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- E, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- F, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- G, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- H, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- I, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ILR Catherwood Library (memos), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ILR School (memos), 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- International Assn. of Fire Fighters, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ILR Labor Historians, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ILR Student Government (Box 1, Folder 24)
- J, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- K, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- L, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Library of Congress, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- M, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Microfilming Corp. of America, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Archives & Libraries Michigan, University of, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- N, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- National Archives & Records Service, U.S., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- New York State Archives, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- O, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- P, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Archives & Libraries Pennsylvania State University, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- R, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- S, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- SUNYLA Newsletter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- T, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Archives & Libraries Tamiment Institute Library, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- U, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- United Electrical Workers, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- United Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Archives & Libraries University of Texas, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- United Mine Workers, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- V (Box 1, Folder 48)
- War on Waste Committee, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Archives & Libraries Wayne State University Library, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- W, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Archives & Libraries Wisconsin State Historical Society, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- X, Y, Z, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- LMDC - Annual Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- LMDC - Annual Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- LMDC - Annual Reports, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- LMDC - Annual Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- LMDC - Annual Reports, 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Annual Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Annual reports, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- LMDC - Monthly Report, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- LMDC - Appraisal & Gifts, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- LMDC - Archives Inventory, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- LMDC - Copying costs, etc., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- LMDC- CUL Promotion Evaluation Comm., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- L.M.D.C. Development Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- LMDC Development Policies, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Equipment, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Expense & Travel, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- LMDC - History, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- LMDC - Personnel - Assoc. Archivist, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Personnel - Full-Time, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- LMDC - Security, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- LMDC - Space, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- LMDC - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 76)